http://www.quadrangle.ca/privacy-policy

Search
Search:
Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy covers Quadrangle Architects Limited website:
The Services and Links of our Website
We respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the information we collect and how we use it. This Policy applies solely to information collected through this website and not other sources.
Conditional Use of this Site
Your access to and use of this website and its contents (the “Site”) is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”), and all applicable laws. By accessing and using this Site, you (the “User” or “you”) accept and agree to these without any limitation or qualification.
Terms of Use
Your use of this Site is also subject to the Terms of Use posted on this Site (“Terms of Use”). Our Web site and/or Blog enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.
Automatic Collection of Information
We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:
Technical administration of the Site
Research and development
Customer administration
Marketing
We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes:
Technical administration of the Site
Research and development
Customer administration
Marketing
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.
We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.
We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.
Confidentiality / Security
We do not give visitors to our Site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Checking your personal information
If you wish to verify, correct, or update any of your personal information collected through this Site, contact us by using the contact form available or by the phone at (416) 598-1240.
COPYRIGHT © 2020
BDP QUADRANGLE
ACCESSIBILITY PRIVACY POLICY
Learn more
×
